Lindsey Murrell

Houston, Texas, United States



murrell8@msu.edu



8106233100



linkedin.com/in/lindsey-murrell

Summary

I have experience writing code in Python, C, C#, C++, HTML, and JavaScript. I graduated with degrees in both Computer Science and Games and Interactive Media, and I minored in Graphic Design as well as Video Game Design and Development. I have three years of experience developing 2D, 3D, and VR games in Unity using C#.

Experience



Software Engineer

METECS

Sep 2022 - Oct 2023 (1 year 2 months)

Game Programmer

Michigan State University

May 2021 - Feb 2023 (1 year 10 months)

I am a programmer at the GEL lab, where we work on various games built for fun and education!

Student Researcher

Michigan State University

Apr 2019 - Feb 2023 (3 years 11 months)

Student Success Mentor

Michigan State University

Aug 2020 - Apr 2021 (9 months)

Education

Michigan State University

Bachelor of Arts - BA, Games and Interactive Media

Jan 2021 - May 2022

Michigan State University

Bachelor of Science - BS, Computer Science

2018 - 2022

Skills

Software Development • Virtual Reality (VR) • C++ • Python (Programming Language) • Java • HTML • JavaScript • C# • Game Development • Unity

Honors & Awards



Hit the Ground Running - METECS

Mar 2023

An award given out for jumping right into my work and making immediate measurable progress.